https://pressalit.com/help-center/privacy-policy/

This website is not supported by Internet Explorer. Please use another browser to get the best performance (E.g. Google Chrome, Firefox, etc.){{ quantity }} Pressalit
Help center Privacy policyPrivacy policyThis privacy policy describes how Pressalit A/S ("Pressalit" or ”we”) collect and use the personal data you leave and/or provide us with when you visit our website and use the various services and functions offered by the website.Collection of personal dataUse of personal data, purpose and reason for processingDeletionConsentSecurityYour rightsLinks to other websitesChanges to privacy policyContact1. Collection of personal dataWe will always inform you, before we collect your personal data. We collect the following information about you, where supplied: name, e-mail address, telephone number, company name, address, postal code, town, country, business area, gender, photograph, education, CV, etc. Be aware that you will need to supply certain personal information in order to use the functions of the website. It will be apparent from the individual forms whether supplying the personal data is mandatory or optional. If supplying the personal data is mandatory, the relevant field will be marked with an asterix (*). If you choose not to supply the personal data requested, you may not be able to use the form as intended. E.g., we do need your contact details to be able to respond to an enquiry from you.If you were supplying personal data that relates to a third party, we would encourage you to get this person’s consent before supplying the data.Personal data is collected when you use the following functions:When you complete our contact formWhen you upload a job applicationWhen you sign up to receive our newsletterWhen you use our digital services such as “find toilet seat by photo”2. Use of personal data, purpose and basis of processingWe collect and use personal data in connection with the functions and purposes that are listed below. We may also process your personal data for other purposes, if we are legally allowed or obliged to do so.For forwarding of newsletterFor processing enquiries or requests from youFor handling of applicationsFor support for and communication with customersFor statistics and analysisFor forwarding of Code of Conduct and policiesFor improving and developing our services on the websiteThe personal data is processed on the following basis:Your consentAs a part of meeting a contractAs a part of the implementation of measures made at your request with a view to concluding a contractTo pursue legitimate interests of Pressalit’sBe aware that you can withdraw your consent at any time, see section 4 below.CookiesWe use cookies on our website to support functionality and to gather insights in order to maintain and develop a good user experience.You can read more detailed information about our use of cookies in our cookie declaration.What are your cookies options?If you do not like the idea of cookies or certain types of cookies, you can opt out by clicking the link below, or you can change your browser's settings to delete cookies that have already been set and to not accept new cookies. To learn more about how to do this, visit the help pages of your browser.Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or do not accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.Change your cookie consentWhere can I find more information about cookies?You can learn more about cookies by visiting the following third party websites:Lifewire.com Browser GuideAll About Cookies.orgNetwork Advertising Initiativeminecookies.org3. DeletionWe delete your personal data when we no longer need them for the above purposes. We may, however, store your personal data for longer in anonymised form or if we are allowed or obliged to by law.4. ConsentWhen you use our website, we sometimes collect and process your personal data with your consent, see section 2 above.Be aware that you can withdraw your consent at any time. You can do this by contacting us (see the contact details in section 9 below).If you withdraw consent, we will stop processing your personal data, unless we are allowed or obliged to continue processing or storing of your personal data on another basis, including under the laws.The withdrawal of your consent will not affect the legality of any processing that has taken place before the withdrawal of consent.If you withdraw your consent, you may not be able to use the functions offered by our website in full any longer.5. SecurityWe have implemented suitable technical and organisational security measures to ensure a satisfactory security level. By doing so we aim to ensure to the best of our ability the quality and integrity of your personal data.6. Your rightsYou have the right to know which personal data we hold that relate to you with certain exceptions that are laid down in legislation.In addition to this, you have the right to object to the collection and further processing of your personal data. Further, you have the right to correction of your personal data or to request the limitation of the uses your personal data are put to.If you request it, we commit to deleting any personal data that we hold relating to you without undue delay, unless we have reason to keep the data on another basis, e.g. if we need them in order to determine a legal requirement or if it is necessary to reply to an enquiry from yourself.In certain circumstances, you have the right to request a copy of the information we have registered regarding you in a structured, commonly accessible and machine-readable format as well as to ask us to transmit this information to another data controller of your choice.If you wish to make use of your rights as described above, you are welcome to contact us (see contact details in section 9 below).For the purpose of any enquiries relating to your rights, we ask that you give us sufficient information to process your enquiry, including your full name and e-mail address, so we can identify you and respond to you request. We commit to replying as soon as possible and no later than a month from the request is received.If you should disagree with the way we process your personal data or the purposes for which we hold them, you are welcome to contact us. You can also make a complaint to:DatatilsynetCarl Jacobsens Vej 352500 ValbyTelephone: +45 33 19 32 00E-mail: dt@datatilsynet.dk7. Links to other websites etc.Our website may contain links to third party websites. We are not responsible for the content of third party websites or for any procedures; such third parties might have for collection and processing or personal data. When you visit a third party website, you should read that website’s privacy policy and any other relevant policies.8. Changes to the privacy policyWe reserve the right to change this privacy policy as necessary to comply with essential changes to the laws, new technical developments, new or improved functions or in order to improve the website.9. ContactIf you would like us to update, correct or delete the personal data we hold for you, or if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you are welcome to contact us at the following address:Pressalit A/SCompany reg. no.: 84364517Pressalitvej 18680 RyDenmarkTelephone: +45 8788 8788E-mail: GDPR@pressalit.comMay 2020*****Pressalit A/SPressalitvej 1DK-8680 RyDanmarkT +45 8788 8788 E pressalit@pressalit.comToilet seatsBathroom accessoriesAccessible bathroomsShower and changing tablesDaycare changing tablesHeight adjustable kitchensHomepagePrivacy policyCookies Country:
{{current.name}}
